JADE HENDRICKS

Summary

I'm a Web developer with over 5 years of professional experience building web applications. I've dabbled in Mobile development with C# and building full stack applications using the MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node) and MEAN stack in my personal capacity. I'm always looking to build the best and most up to date software on the market.

Skills

- React (Proficient)
- Angular (Proficient)
- JavaScript (Expert)

- NodeJS, Express, MongoDB (Proficient)
- HTML 5 (Expert)
- CSS 3 / SCSSS / SASS / LESS (Expert)

Experience

Full Stack - 06/2018 to 02/2020

Front-end developer/Mobile, Cape Town, South Africa

- Working in teams of 4 8 developers in order to build Fulltack/Mobile applications.
- Working on up to 3 projects at the same time with different development teams.
- Management duties associated with being part of the company's management committee.

Itopia Interactive- 04/2016 to 12/2017

Junior Front-end developer, Cape Town, South Africa

- Working in development team of 4 to build out designs from designers.
- Building CMS applications for clients.

Isoflow - 09/2015 to 12/2015

Front-end developer Internship, Cape Town, South Africa

Working in a team of UI/UX designers to developer their designs into functional web applications.

Education

National Diploma: **National Diploma in Multimedia Technology** - 2015 **Cape Peninsula University of technology**, Cape Town, South Africa

References

Andrew La Grange (Full Stack): Andrew.lagrange@fullstack.co.za

Kurt Samson (Itopia Interactive): kurt@itopia.co.za